Labyrinth Story.
Cicerone.
Where are you?
Labyrinth ♪ Labyrinthos
The name, "Cicerone", did
your father give him that name?
Cicerone named himself that.
I see.
It's a very fancy name.
I found you.
This time, it's Sachi's turn.
Not yet.
I'm ready.
Come here.
Cicerone.
Come here, Cicerone.
Sachi?
Satchan.
Satchan. Satchan. Satchan.
Satchan. Satchan. Satchan. Satchan.
Neko-machi Alley.
"Here, come in, you two..."
The Running Man.
Left and right engine outputs nominal.
Pressure level normal.
Heart rate increasing.
Perspiration increasing.
Brain waves, no abnormalities.
At the time, due to a request
from a certain magazine,
I was writing an article on Zach Hugh.
The brutal race, which sends
countless racers to their deaths,
Death Circus.
As its champion, Zach Hugh was the man who
reigned on its throne for nearly ten years.
His magnificent, death-defying
control of his machine
drove the audience wild.
Zach the Grim Reaper.
The Immortal Man.
He was given many names.
However...
Contact spacing, unstable.
Heart rate, perspiration, still increasing.
Ocular response declining.
At that point, the repeated
strain of the brutal race
had already destroyed his mind and body.
He's reached his limits.
He can't take the shock
from the machine any longer.
It's not possible to continue any longer.
Have him forfeit.
Chief, he's not slowing down.
What?!
This is unbelievable...
Chief!
Look!
After crossing the goal, his machine
continued to accelerate even more.
He continued to run.
Zach Hugh.
He was a great champion.
But, his death is still
shrouded in mystery.
You know that five days ago a
coup occurred in the Aloana Republic?
Yes.
I'm sure you're also aware that in the
country's Piraru River region's jungle
our company's 444th
construction project is progressing?
Yes.
This project is a strategic step for us to achieve
a foothold in the resource rich Aloana Republic.
But, three days ago, Aloana's
new government sent us
a unilateral decision to
cancel the construction contract.
Do you understand?
I see.
No, you don't see!
It's been cancelled! Cancelled!
That construction project's been cancelled!
Construction Cancellation Order.
Mister, you just ran a light.
According to the notice
we must cease the construction
immediately and, in addition
get this, the deferred payment for the breach of
contract is going to be made over twenty years.
Twenty years?!
It is true that #444 is
quite a difficult construction.
The designated area is a swampland
sandwiched by higher ground.
When the rainy season comes,
the whole area turns into a river.
And when the water recedes,
next comes the vegetation.
It grows like a monster and turns the place
back into a jungle in less than six months.
It's an unreal place!
Ah, I see.
Construction #444 began with the
appropriation of an enormous budget.
Currently, it's still proceeding
to expend an enormous budget.
Before the losses spread any further,
we must cease operations immediately
and pull our assets out.
Then you should instruct the site...
We sent the cancellation
order out to the site manager...
Well, then...
The day we sent the cancellation order
he disappeared and we haven't
had any communication since.
He's missing?
Because of the way
the construction site is,
we depend solely on
robots for the labour force.
The only human being there was
the man who was the site manager.
Then...
Even as we speak, those damn puppet robots
are taking expensive materials
and chucking them into the mud.
Finding the missing
previous foreman and halting
the 444th construction project immediately
is the reason why you are being dispatched.
We're counting on you, Sugioka.
Yes, Sir.
What is that?
Safety First.
Would you be the foreman, sir?
This place is unbelievable.
Please state your name and employee number.
Oh! Ah! Hey! What are you doing?!
Well then, mister, call us when
you're done with your work here!
We'll be by to pick you up!
Uh, you're going already?!
Hey, wait a...
Mister, be careful!
Wait! Wait!
Hey! You!
What are they in a hurry for?
If they've broken the camera or something
I'm going to have them replace it.
They've got to be kidding.
Who knows what people
lacking culture think.
I agree.
I require confirmation of
name and employee number.
Yeah, what was the name of the
previous foreman that disappeared?
Do you know where he went?
If you do not state your name
and your employee number
it means that you are not the
recognised as the proper foreman.
If you are not recognised as the
proper foreman, then you will be
considered unrelated to the construction...
Anyway, show me to the dormitory.
You can give me the details there.
Or possibly someone who intends to
interfere with the construction efforts
and will be repelled and...
Tsutomu Sugioka.
Employee number CX88.
Confirmation... completed.
Welcome, for having come
from so far Mr. Foreman.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
I am #1 of 444...
...is how it is done.
Orders regarding construction
#444 are all transmitted from myself
to other robots in charge.
Oh, good grief.
They're working at it so hard.
All the foreman's orders
must go through me as well.
If we do not use this system, the chain
of command will be thrown into chaos.
Well, I want you to use that system and convey
to all the robots the new foreman's orders.
It has been decided that this
construction is to be cancelled.
Cease work immediately and...
Hey! Wait a second!
I'm not done with my orders yet!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
You!
What's the meaning of this!
Hey!
Mr. Foreman must be
exhausted by the long journey,
so I will take my leave for today.
Why do you need to lock the door! You!
This area is rife with harmful
insects and this is for your safety.
In any case, open this door!
Hey!
You!
Do you understand me!
Furthermore, tomorrow, your schedule
Come back!
Is on the wall schedule chart.
Hey!
Don't you understand I'm
telling you to come back!
Open this!
Shit!
Please help me! I'm going to be killed! That robot is insane! To my wife, Sachiko. I'm not going to make it. I love you!
I wanted to do it one more time. Tooru, listen to your mother. Study hard and become an upstanding human being. O...
Don't you understand!
Open it!
Hey!
Breakfast will be until
30 minutes past the hour.
At 45 minutes past the hour until 10:25 will
be an inspection tour of the first site.
At 10:30, in the reference room...
See, it is right over there
where the construction
is delayed the most; The 8th district.
Hey! What's wrong with that robot?
It's overheated.
The work is very harsh so
his circuits must have given out.
Ridiculous!
How much do you think
that single robot costs?!
It's more expensive than an airliner!
The work is experiencing delays so I
am having the robots work at full capacity.
My job is to ensure that the construction
is completed by the date it's due.
Some sacrifices are unavoidable.
There is no due date anymore!
More importantly, we have
to minimise the losses...
The due date is in one month.
The work is suffering delays so I am
having the robots work at full capacity...
What? What's wrong with you?
Oh, are you angry?
Next, we will inspect district 10.
This way, Mr. Foreman.
W... Wait just a moment, please.
Breakfast will be until
30 minutes past the hour.
At 45 minutes past the hour until 10:25 will
be an inspection tour of the first site.
At 10:30, in the reference room,
please examine the previous.
What's this?
Month's construction reports and paperwork.
At 12:30...
It is about time for the
inspection tour, Mr. Foreman.
Hey! Wait!
I can't take this any more!
Make a fool of a human!
Even though I'm normally quiet...
The rainy season is
approaching so beginning today
the robots' workload has been increased.
Who made that order?!
There has been a slight
increase in the loss of robots,
but the rate of construction has increased.
Please be delighted.
A slight increase in the loss of...
How many?!
Today, there have been twenty units.
Tomorrow, there are
twenty-four units scheduled.
We can't just let you
trash those robots like that!
Listen carefully, you puppet robot!
Get this! This construction has
been issued a cancellation order!
Cease immediately! Do you understand?!
I judge that statement as an intent to
interfere with the current construction.
Any statements made by you
from here on will have no effect.
Shut up! I told you to stop!
Stop, you stupid robot!
That which interferes with the progress
of the construction must be removed.
Removed?
Beginning today for an indefinite term
the Foreman's inspection tours
of the sites will be cancelled.
This is madness.
Please help me! I'm going to be killed! That robot is insane! To my wife, Sachiko. I'm not going to make it. I love you!
I wanted to do it one more time. Tooru, listen to your mother. Study hard and become an upstanding human being. O...
Good morning.
I have brought you your meal.
Yes!
Even if you destroy me,
the construction will progress.
We must complete it before
the deadline no matter...
what... progress...
Damn it!
Bastard!
No good!
The puppet robots are still working.
As I thought.
This one's just a terminal.
I need to destroy the system core
or the robots won't stop working.
If I follow this cable...
Emergency communique! An emergency
communique from corporate headquarters!
Early dawn today, there was a
second coup in the new government
of the Aloana Republic and power has
been restored to the former government.
Earlier, there was a press conference
by the former government Damn it!
To announce the resumption of the
444th construction contract. Damn it!
I repeat.
It has been decided that the 444th
construction project will continue. Damn it!
Tsutomu Sugioka!
It's me!
Section chief, Maruyama!
Hey!
Tsutomu Sugioka!
It's me!
Respond!
Hey!
Hey! Sugioka!
Welcome.